FUNMILOLA AJOKE AKINDEHIN

E7/170 Aliwo Gate, Ibadan - Ibadan

□ +234 8037700316 • ☐ funmilolakindehin@gmail.com DOB: 29 March, 1992 Sex: Female Status: Single

I am interested in using my acquired skill, knowledge and experience to establish a career in a professionally challenging environment where I can contribute positively and significantly to the growth and success of the organization while maintaining a good social and interpersonal communication in a team that is constantly achieving and surpassing the goals of the organization.

Previous Employment

Feedwell Supermarket Limited

IBADAN, OYO STATE

Inventory officer

March 2020-To Date

I prepared purchase orders, received, stored and issued goods, managed stock level and distributed supplies from stock to different outlets.

Quztan Hotel and Suites

IBADAN. OYO STATE

Accountant

October 2019-March 2020

I carried out balancing of the daily account books, receiving of cash from clients and dispensing of cash for daily operation of the hotel.

DAWLS INTEGRATED NIG. LTD.

BODIJA, IBADAN, OYO STATE

Secretary

October 2015-November 2016

I carried out data entry and documentation, received clients daily in a courteous manner, handled incoming and out going calls and also took care of the general office and computer upkeep.

GIONEE MOBILE

IBADAN OYO STATE

Promoter

December 2014-August 2015

I sold and promoted a variety of customer's product using sales outlets. I made a documentation of the weekly sales, participated in promotional campaigns to boost sales, attended to customers enquires about product features and complaints and also prospected for new customers.

Education

Rufus Giwa polytechnic

Owo, Ondo State

2019

Federal polytechnic, Ede

Anglican Grammar School

Ede, Osun State

ND Accountancy,

HND Accountancy,

Igbara oke, Ondo State

SSCE/WAEC,

iguara oke, Ondo State

2001

2014

Technical and Personal skills

- o **General Skills:** Computer skills, microsoft office products, presentation skills, leadership skills, team playing skills, inter-personal skills, pro activeness, communication skills.
- Other: Documentation and report writing, planning, quick thinking, fast learning, standard office equipment operations.

Interests and extra-curricular activity

o Reading, dancing, listening to music and singing.